https://medievalpottery.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Copyright statement
All images and text used in the design of this website are copyright of the Medieval Pottery Research Group, 2001-2019. They must not be reproduced without written permission.
Who we are
We are the Medieval Pottery Research Group, MPRG, Registered Charity (UK Registered Charity No.1018513). Our website address is: https://www.medievalpottery.org.uk.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
All personal data is collected in full compliance with the General Data Protection Regulations.
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
|Privacy PolicyHome
News – The latest news from MPRG.
Conference Gallery – Livorno 2006 (SPMA Conference)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 1 (1977)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 2 (1978)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 3 (1979)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 4 (1980)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 5 (1981)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 6 (1982)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 7 (1983)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 8 (1984)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 9 (1985)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 10 (1986)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 11 (1987)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 12 (1988)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 13 (1989)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 14 (1990)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 15 (1991)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 16 (1992)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 17 (1993)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 18 (1994)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 19 (1995)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 20 (1996)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 21 (1997)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 22-3 (1998-99)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 24 (2000)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 25 (2001)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 28 (2004)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 29 (2005)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 30 (2006-2008)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 31 (2010)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 33 (2012)
© 2020 Medieval Pottery Research Group   |   Website by GilesCarey
MENU
Navigation
Ceramic Reference Collection Lists (from MPRG Standards)
Conference Gallery – Livorno 2006 (SPMA Conference)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 1 (1977)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 10 (1986)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 11 (1987)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 12 (1988)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 13 (1989)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 14 (1990)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 15 (1991)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 16 (1992)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 17 (1993)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 18 (1994)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 19 (1995)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 2 (1978)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 20 (1996)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 21 (1997)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 22-3 (1998-99)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 24 (2000)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 25 (2001)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 28 (2004)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 29 (2005)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 3 (1979)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 30 (2006-2008)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 31 (2010)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 33 (2012)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 4 (1980)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 5 (1981)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 6 (1982)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 7 (1983)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 8 (1984)
Medieval Ceramics Volume 9 (1985)
Medieval Ceramics 29, 2005 (test)
Search for:
